Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Latinas - Antonia Hernandez -- 9/13/1994, 33 (Box 15)
- Latinas -- 10/16/1994, 34 (Box 15)
- Latinas -- 9/15/1994, 35 (Box 15)
- 1199 Strike - H Hospital, Middletown -- August 10, 1990, 36 (Box 15)
- Moe -- Reel 8, 37 (Box 15)
- Camp Vacamas, 38 (Box 15)
- Hilda -- R-10, 39 (Box 15)
- Metzger, 40 (Box 15)
- Our backyard, 1 (Box 16)
- Still Going Strong: The Retired Members of Local 1199, 1992; 2 (Box 16)
  Bread and Roses Cultural Project, Inc. (1992)
- Communications Workers of America -- Fasanella, 3 (Box 16)
- Channel 7 News, 4 (Box 16)
- To the Brink: Risking all at the Daily News, 1990-91, 1991; 5 (Box 16)
  Off-Line Edit
- Latin Women of Hope, 6 (Box 16)
- Women of Hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, 7 (Box 16)
- Members in Action -- Service Employees International Union -- Convention '96, 1996; 8 (Box 16)
  Organizing: San Jose; Taking it to the streets: Hamilton, Ont.; Bargaining for dignity: Milwaukee; Building Power at work: Seattle; SEIU: the Early Years
- Channel 7: Tiempo Latina - Women of Hope; Channel 13: Women of Hope, 9 (Box 16)
- Communications Workers of America -- Fasanella, 10 (Box 16)
- Ralph Fasanella video by Glen Pearcy, 11 (Box 16)
- DC - 4/5/1992; 4/22/1992, 12 (Box 16)
- Women of Hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, 1996; 13 (Box 16)
  Bread and Roses Cultural Project -- 1996
- Fasanella, 14 (Box 16)
  Glen Pearcy Productions
- 1199: The History of a Fighting Union, 15 (Box 16)
- 1199: History of a Fighting Union, 16 (Box 16)
  Produced by Moe Foner
- Moe Foner Interviewed by Melvin McCray (6/12/1999), 17 (Box 16)
  Media Genesis Productions 3 Agate Court, Brooklyn, New York
- Bread and Roses -- Marc Levin Loftland Productions, 18 (Box 16)
  Protection Master
- Title is illegible, 19 (Box 16)
- Labor Day -- Bread and Roses (9/3/1979), 1 (Box 17)
- Marc Levin, 2 (Box 17)
- Interview Jane Fonda/Tom Hayden -- #1199 (12 March 1979), 3 (Box 17)
- 1199 at Biltmore --, 4 (Box 17)
  Tape #2 - Camera: Diablo/Marc; Sound: Mike; VCT: George; Lights: Emilo -- MASTER
- 1199 at Biltmore (6/Feb 1979), 5 (Box 17)
  Tape #3 - Camera: Marc; Sound: George; VCR: Mike; Lights: Emilo -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses -- Noonies Place -- 1199 Plaza, 6 (Box 17)
- 1199 at Biltmore (Feb. 6, 1978), 7 (Box 17)
  Tape #1 -- Camera: Marc; Sound: Mike; VCR: George; Lights: Emilo -- MASTER
- Labor Day - Block Party (3 Sept. 1979), 8 (Box 17)
  #1 -- MASTER
- NFLPA: A Piece of the Pie, 9 (Box 17)
  SUB MASTER with titles and Id's
- Media Works -- Incomplete, 10 (Box 17)
  Production Reel
- Gene Upshaw -- Voice-Over -- Channel 2, 11 (Box 17)
- NFLPA - Piece of the Pie, 12 (Box 17)
  Edited MASTER - without titles and Id's
- Podd Campaign --, 13 (Box 17)
  Work Print
- Campaign for American 80, 14 (Box 17)
- Freed Tape, 15 (Box 17)
- Excerpts from work of Marc Levin, 16 (Box 17)
  1.Why work?; 2.Campaign for America; 3.Mobia's Trip -- Tape #5 -- New Years Eve 1980
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE, 17 (Box 17)
  Tape 3-B -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses -- TS at 1199 Plaza, 18 (Box 17)
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE --, 19 (Box 17)
  Tape 5-B -- MASTER
- Handwritten notes about the tapes, 20 (Box 17)
- Hispanic Heritage Month Feature: Ana Sol Guiterrez, 1 (Box 18)
- 17B, 2 (Box 18)
- PR Fuutse - 21-A, 3 (Box 18)
  Duplicate
- PF Fuutse, 4 (Box 18)
- Women of Hope Latinas Abriendo Camino, 5 (Box 18)
  Closed Caption on Line 21
- Drems Ensamal, 6 (Box 18)
- Furest Photos, 7 (Box 18)
- Hispanic Heritage Month Feature: and Sol Gutierrez, 8 (Box 18)
  tape #4
- Latinas Flat Art #2, 9 (Box 18)
- Archives PR, 10 (Box 18)
- Parade PR 94 -- 8/12/1994, 11 (Box 18)
- School Board Meeting 39, 12 (Box 18)
- Bread and Roses: One hour documentary on 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project, 1980; 13 (Box 18)
- When Theater was a Weapon, 14 (Box 18)
  sample reel
- Holographic Films, Take Care, Program Reel, 15 (Box 18)
- I Am Somebody, 16 (Box 18)
- On the Move, 17 (Box 18)
  Dub
- B & R Day, 18 (Box 18)
- Bread & Roses, 19 (Box 18)
- B & R Day, 20 (Box 18)
- WTC, 1 (Box 19)
- Bread & Roses Too, 2 (Box 19)
  Answer Print
- Bread & Roses Too -- #9, 3 (Box 19)
- Like a Beautiful Child / John Schultz, 4 (Box 19)
  Print #5
- Moe Foner: Hospital Strike, 5 (Box 19)
- Unlabeled Audio-tape, 1 (Box 20)
- Seth Eisman Doc. Establishing, 2 (Box 20)
- District 1199 Hospital Workers Union -- 7/16/1981, 3 (Box 20)
  #460 -- 1-Know Them, 2-Recovery, 3-Environment
- District 1199 National Hospital Workers Union - Radio Spot -- 60 Second "Know Them By Name", 4 (Box 20)
  #459
- Interviews with 1199 Retirees for still montage -- Aug. 9, 1979, 5 (Box 20)
  Out takes
- Interviews of 1199 Retirees, 6 (Box 20)
  Out takes -- 6169-445
- Helping to Care: Dist. 1100, 7 (Box 20)
- Night Seth Eisman Pix Selects, 8 (Box 20)
  3 reels in one box
- 1930's Strike, 9 (Box 20)
- Practical Dreamer, 10 (Box 20)
- 1930's Strike, 11 (Box 20)
- Still Going Strong / Bread & Roses Cultural -- 12/26/1991, 12 (Box 20)
- A Message to Hospital Workers from Martin Luther King, Jr., 447 (Box 21)
  4 copies - These were found in box 22 and moved with the other items in that box to the Artificial collection 6349 AV, box 1 -- 515--103--e--5--c
- Ossie & Ruby and Bread and Roses, 1 (Box 22)
  3 copies -- housed in Artificial collection 6349 AV, box 1 -- 515--103--e--5--c
- The Union Democracy Built, 2 (Box 22)
- 6169-192, 1 (Box 23)
- 6169-191, 2 (Box 23)
- 6169-194, 3 (Box 23)
- 6169-193, 4 (Box 23)
- 6169-196, 5 (Box 23)
- 6169-195, 6 (Box 23)
- 6169-198, 7 (Box 23)
- 6169-197, 8 (Box 23)
- Practical Dreamer -- 6169-310, 9 (Box 23)
- Practical Dreamer -- 6169-310, 10 (Box 23)
- 24-A -- 6169-180, 11 (Box 23)
  duplicate
- Coretta Scott King - A message to Hospital and Nursing Home Workers, 12 (Box 23)
  3 copies of 33-1/3 RPM disc -- removed from 6169 P
- Bread & Roses Too -- #2 CRI Check Print, 1 (Box 24)
- LJ Davis - District 1199 -- April 2, 1982, 2 (Box 24)
  1" MASTER
- Bread & Roses - Invisible No More -- 6/22/1992, 3 (Box 24)
  English/Spanish subtitles
- Take Care, 4 (Box 24)
- Take Care, 1989; 5 (Box 24)
  MASTER -- 6/25/1989
- Unlabeled Betacam SP tape, 6 (Box 24)
- Unlabeled Betacam SP tape, 7 (Box 24)
- Like a Beautiful Child (Box 25)
  - Like a Beautiful Child (Box 25)
- 20405-5 (Box 26)
- Bread & Roses Too (Box 27)
  - Bread & Roses Too -- #4 (Box 27)
- Hospital Strike (Box 28)
  - Hospital Strike -- Print #3-75 (Box 28)
- Ossie & Ruby and Bread & Roses (Box 29)
- Ossie and Ruby and Bread and Roses (Box 30)
- Ossie and Ruby and Bread and Roses (Box 31)
- Sekunjalo: Bread and Roses (Box 32)
- Not Bread Alone: A Conference on Workers Culture (Box 33)
- Bread & Roses (Box 34)
  1000 #2 (141 Pulses)
- Half Hour segments (Box 35)
- NYC Labor Chorus (Box 36)
  1. Lift every voice; 2.This old hammer; 3. De Colres; 4. Solidarity; 5. Common threads; 6. Roll the union on; 7. Blue skies
- Seeger singing De Colores (Box 37)
- Ambos a dos -- FC 7854 (Box 40)
- En mi Viejo San Juan (Box 41)
  tone 1 -- 6169-456
- Latinas - Full Mix - Mono (Box 42)
- Talisman - La Tina -- 10/3/1995 (Box 43)
- Apollo II Highlights -- 5/17/1995 (Box 44)
- Loose Woman -- RH-335 / by Sandra Cisneros -- June 5, 1995 (Box 45)
- Latinas - Split Mix (Box 46)
- Teenagers (Box 47)
  tape 1 -- MASTER
- Teenager (Box 48)
  tape 2 -- MASTER
- Teenager (Box 49)
  tape 3 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 51)
  tape 4 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 52)
  tape 5 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 52)
  tape 7 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 53)
  tape 6 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 54)
  tape 8 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 55)
  tape 9 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 56)
  tape 10 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 57)
  tape 11 -- MASTER
- Teenagers (Box 58)
  tape 12 -- MASTER
- 1199 League - Childcare Conference - 6/1/1991 (Box 59)
  MASTER -- tape 1
- 1199 - League Childcare Conference -- 6/1/1991 (Box 60)
  MASTER -- tape 2
- 1199 League Conference -- 6/1/1991 (Box 61)
  MASTER -- tape 3
- Benefit Fund -- 3/3/1991 (Box 62)
- Benefits Fund -- 4/1991 (Box 63)
  MASTER -- tape 5
- Benefits - 6/19/1991 (Box 64)
  MASTER -- tape 6
- Benefits -- 6/19/1991 (Box 65)
  MASTER -- tape 7
- Benefits -- 6/22/1991 (Box 66)
  MASTER -- tape 8
- Benefits -- 7/11/1991 (Box 67)
  MASTER -- tape 9
- Benefit tape -- 7/11/1991 (Box 68)
  MASTER -- tape 10
- Benefits tape -- 7/12/1991 (Box 69)
  MASTER -- tape 11
- Benefits -- 10/16/1991 (Box 70)
  Tape 12
- Benefits -- 10/16/1991 (Box 71)
  tape 13
- Benefits -- 10/17/1991 (Box 72)
  tape 14
- Benefits -- 10/17/1991 (Box 73)
  tape 15
- Benefits -- 10/17/1991 (Box 74)
  tape 16
- Benefits --10/17/1991 (Box 75)
  tape 17
- Benefits -- 1/9/1992 (Box 76)
  tape 18
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 77)
  tape 1 -- 2-13-1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 78)
  tape 2 -- 2/13/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 79)
  tape 3 -- 3/1/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 80)
  tape 4 - 3/4/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 81)
  tape 5 -- 3/4/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 82)
  tape 6 -- 3/12/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 83)
  tape 7 -- 3/12/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 84)
  tape 8 -- 5/7/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 85)
  tape 9 -- 5/7/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 86)
  tape 10 -- 5/7/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 87)
  tape 11 -- 5/12/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 88)
  tape 12 -- 5/12/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 89)
  tape 13 -- 5/12/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 90)
  tape 14 -- 6/20/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 91)
  tape 15 -- 6/20/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 92)
  tape 16 -- 6/20/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 93)
  tape 17 -- 6/21/1992
- 1199 - Political Actions (Box 94)
- 1199 - Political Actions, 1992 (Box 95)
  tape 19 -- 6/21/1992
- Re-Training Office (Box 96)
  Reel 7
- Benefit Fund - tape #2 (Box 97)
- 4/30/1991 - WTC Demonstration (Box 98)
- 1199 Benefits - Tape 1 (Box 99)
- Leon Davis Memorial (Box 100)
  tape 1
- Leon Davis Memorial -- 10/5/1992 (Box 101)
- T & U Graduates, 1991 (Box 102)
  MASTER -- 6/13/1991
- T & U Grad, 1991 (Box 103)